walkme.com 2016-10-25

# Privacy Policy - WalkMe

**INTRODUCTION  
**** ** At WalkMe Inc. (“we”, “us”, “our” or “WalkMe”) we are committed to protecting any data that we collect concerning you when you use or register on our website located at [www.walkme.com](http://www.walkme.com/) (the “Site”) or by using our online product known as “WalkMe System” which is available on the Site (the “Software”). Please note that this Privacy Policy applies to the information that we collect through the Site and the Software. By using our site or the Software you agree to the use of the data that we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy, as may be amended.

 **COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
**Our primary goals in collecting personal information are to provide you with the products and services made available through the Site, including, but not limited, to the Software, to communicate with you, and to manage your registered user account, if you have one. When you register on our site or use the Software, we ask for information such as your name, company name or affiliation, password, email address and telephone number (your “Personal Information”).

Furthermore, WalkMe collects the email addresses of people who communicate with WalkMe via email, create accounts or post a public question on the Website forum. When you post content on or through the Site by way of public posts or survey information etc., please keep in mind that any Personal Information you post may be viewed by others.

If you decide to become a paying customer for the Software, WalkMe may collect additional information from you, including but not limited to billing and account information for credit cards, payment cards or other payment systems and share this information with WalkMe’s billing and payment processor(s). WalkMe does not store credit card or payment card numbers after they have been forwarded to its billing and payment processor(s), unless it is necessary for providing the Software.

WalkMe may also receive information about you from our business partners with which you have an account, service relationship or transaction history. Furthermore, WalkMe may receive Personal Information from third parties when you authorize such third parties to authenticate or identify you to WalkMe or sign in to the Software using credentials from a third party service.

 **TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**  
WalkMe and our partners **,** affiliates, or analytics or service providers, use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the website, tracking users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis.

We use cookies for storing users’ settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication and for improving the user experience on our website. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited.

We use Local Storage such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5.

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

 **LOG DATA**  
When you use our Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). Such information may include IP addresses, browser type, referral URL’s, language information, the domain from which you are visiting and additional information in respect to your usage and browsing of the Site and the Software. Except as set forth herein we do not use this information to personally identify you, but rather use it to monitor the use of the Site and the Software, including for (i) technical administration for the Site (ii) to help determine which users have access privilege to certain content, services or recourses that the Company offer, estimate and report total audience size and traffic, help combat fraud and abuse and provide analytics and reporting in respect to the use of the Software.

 **HOW INFORMATION IS USED**  
WalkMe uses the information it collects from you to deliver WalkMe services to you and continuously enhance your user experience. Generally speaking, we use the collected information to communicate with you, fulfill your requests, customize the content, improve our products and services, protect our and your rights, and comply with laws and regulations.

We may use your personal information to send you promotional information and updates regarding WalkMe and its products and services. You may choose not to receive such information and opt-out of such future communications. All such communications sent to you will contain the instructions for opting-out. In addition to these optional email messages, WalkMe may contact you via any email address you provide to us with transactional or relationship messages such as account status messages, security updates or notifications of changes in the terms of your account or the WalkMe Services. These types of transactional or relationship email messages are not optional.

 **WITH WHOM INFORMATION IS SHARED**  
WalkMe does not share Personal Information collected from your use of the Site with others, except as described in this Privacy Policy.  
_Public Information_  
WalkMe may share as it sees fit information that you voluntarily make public, including information that you post on any blogs, message boards, chat rooms or other similar forums, whether or not such forums are owned by WalkMe. Since such public information can be accessed by the public and used by any member of the public, such use by third parties is beyond the control of WalkMe. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at support@walkme.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

We also display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at support@walkme,com.  
_Personal Information_  
WalkMe may share Personal Information under the following circumstances: (1) In the course of operating our business, it may be necessary or appropriate for us to provide access to your Personal Information to others such as our service providers, contractors and select vendors so that we can operate the WalkMe Service and our business. Where practical, we seek to obtain confidentiality agreements that are consistent with this Privacy Policy and that limit others’ use or disclosure of this Personal Information; and/or (2) We may share your Personal Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, to establish or exercise our legal rights, to defend against legal claims or in such circumstances where, in our judgment, disclosure is required or appropriate in accordance with applicable laws and regulations; and/or (3) We may share your Personal Information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our various terms of service or as otherwise required by law; and/or (4) As we continue to develop our business, we may sell all or part of our business. In such transactions, Personal Information collected from users is generally one of the business assets that will be transferred. The transferred Personal Information will remain subject to this Privacy Policy or subsequent policies to which you have consented.

Furthermore, if you chose to subscribe to the Software, WalkMe uses the services of a credit card processing company to bill our users for subscription fees. These third parties do not retain, share or store this personal information or its part other than for providing these services and are bound by strict agreements limiting their use of such information.

 **HOW INFORMATION IS PROTECTED**  
Your WalkMe accounts may be secured by member-created passwords, in which case reasonable precautions are taken to ensure that your account information is kept private. You are responsible for keeping your passwords confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.  
No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.  
WalkMe uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the WalkMe Service. Where practical, we seek to obtain confidentiality agreements that are consistent with this Privacy Policy and that limit others’ use or disclosure of your Personal Information.

 **USER ACCESS AND CHOICE  
**If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, ask to have it removed from a public forum, directory or testimonial on our site or deactivate it by emailing our Customer Support at support@walkme.com or by contacting us by telephone at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

 **DATA RETENTION  
**We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

 **INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER OF INFORMATION**  
Please be aware that information you provide to us or we obtain as a result of your use of the Site or the Software, may be processed and transferred all countries in which WalkMe has offices and operations and be subject to applicable law. This information may also be processed by staff working for us or for one of our suppliers. The privacy and data protection laws in such countries may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. By using our website or any of the Software, or by providing us with your information, you consent to this collection, transfer, storage, and processing of information to and in countries.

 **INFORMATION RELATING TO CHILDREN  
**We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from children under the age of 13 or knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to register for the WalkMe Service. If you are under 13, do not register or attempt to register for any of the WalkMe Service or send any information about yourself to us. No one under the age of 13 may provide any Personal Information to, on or through the WalkMe Service. If we learn that we have collected or have been sent Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that Personal Information as soon as reasonably practical. If you believe that we might have collected or been sent Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, please contact our Support team as soon as possible.

 **THIRD PARTY LINKS**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Site. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Site and welcome and feedback about these sites.

 **SOCIAL MEDIA WIDGETS  
**Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, and Widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These Features may collect your internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

 **SERVICE PLATFORM SCOPE  
**The use of information collected through WalkMe service platform (“WalkMe Service Platform”) shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client which contracted with WalkMe for the use of the Walkme Service Platform (“Client”) has engaged WalkMe.

WalkMe does not intend to collect personal data through its service platform (as opposed to WalkMe website, where WalkMe may collect personal information you choose to provide as described under the paragraph titled, “COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION”). However, since it is possible for personal information to end up in the Service Platform and , since WalkMe has no direct relationship with the  end users (“End User(s)”) who use WalkMe Service Platform, it is stated that should any such user choose to post personal data to WalkMe, against WalkMe’s directions, WalkMe will not claim responsibility for adding security controls needed for that specific data type, and it will be secure under the same guidelines and using the same controls as for non-personal data. WalkMe will remove any personal data posted by end users upon discovering it.

An End User who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the respective relelvant WalkMe Client (the data controller) through which such End User was provided access to the Walkme Service Platform. If requested in accordance with the foregoing to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe. **_ _**

We will retain data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. WalkMe will retain data as much as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

 ** ** **TRUSTe SCOPE  
**The TRUSTe program covers private information that is collected by WalkMe through this website, [www.walkme.com](http://www.walkme.com/) and the WalkMe service platform.In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe, please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.

 **U.S.-E.U./SWISS SAFE HARBOR  
**WalkMe complies with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union member countries and Switzerland. WalkMe has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Priniciples of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view WalkMe’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
WalkMe reserves the right to update and change this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice or acceptance by you, so please check this page frequently for updates and changes. If we make any material changes we will notify you or our Client by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. Your continued use signifies your acceptance to any change in this policy.Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section on our Site, establishing the use, disclaimers and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

 **QUESTIONS  
**Any questions  **or comments**  about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to  

WalkMe Inc.  
22 4th st.  
San Francisco, CA  
94103

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 12/27/2015
